http://www.visionenhancers.co.uk/pages/privacy-policy

Magnifying Glasses
Hand Held Magnifying GlassesMagnifying Glass with LightsPocket Magnifying GlassesBar MagnifiersDome MagnifiersStand MagnifiersHands Free MagnifiersClip-On MagnifiersFolding MagnifiersMagnifying SpectaclesRound the Neck MagnifiersElectronic / Video MagnifiersBinocularsMonocularsProducts By Use
Anti Glare Low Vision AidsLow Vision Aids for CraftsLow Vision Aids for Looking at PhotosLow Vision Aids for Personal CareLow Vision Aids for Sporting EventsModel Painting Magnifiers and LampsReading Aids for Low VisionVision Aids for Seeing in the DistanceVitamins and Eye CareWriting Aids for The Visually ImpairedVision Aid for Watching TV - TV MagnifierProducts By Brand
Bierley MagnifiersCarsonCoil MagnifiersDaylight LampsD-ClipsEschenbach MagnifiersImproVision Filter SunglassesMagnif EyesOptelec MagnifiersOptima Low Vision MagnifiersSchweizer MagnifiersSpecwellProducts By Magnification
1.25x Magnifiers1.5x Magnifiers2.0x Magnifiers2.25x Magnifiers2.5x Magnifiers3.0x Magnifiers4.0x Magnifiers5.0x Magnifiers6.0x Magnifiers7.0x Magnifiers9.0x Magnifiers10.0x Magnifiers12x Magnifiers14-15x MagnifiersOver 20.0x MagnifiersMagnification FinderBlogs
About Eye ConditionsAbout Macular ConditionsLiving With Macular ConditionsMagnifiers and Low Vision AidsContact Us
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.
Topics:
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use the information about you?
Marketing
Access to your information and correction
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
Copyright notice
How to contact us
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.
We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website.
If you agree, we shall pass on your personal information to our group of companies so that they may offer you their products and services.
Vision Enhancers will not share your information for marketing purposes with outside companies.
In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.
Marketing
We would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies in our group which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.
You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes.
If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, contact us. Or preferable, unsubscribe using the link provided in marketing materials.
Access to your information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email support@visionenhancers.co.uk. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org
You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 30 April 2019.
Copyright notice
This website and its content is copyright © of Vision Enhancers. All rights reserved.
Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:
you may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only
you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material
You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.
Subscribe to our newsletter
Subscribe and receive news about products and special offers
Unsubscribe any time!
Free Delivery to UK, EU, USA, Canada and Mexico
Tracked shipping available to rest of the world.
Satisfied or refunded
We're happy to exchange or refund the cost of items returned within 14 days of dispatch date  returned in resaleable condition in the original packaging.
Top-notch support
Chat with us or send us a message
Secure payments
Your order is safe and secure
